(Leonard:)...because they would've
already wanted you...
(Leonard:)...before they, you know, got you.
(Sheldon:)From the mind that brought you hi-lo.
(Sheldon:)Let me show you to your room.
(Elizabeth:)All right, I guess I am tired.
(Elizabeth:)-Good night, Leonard.
-Sleep night.
(Leonard:)I mean, obviously, good night.
(Leonard:)I started to say sleep tight.
Then I changed my mind in the middle.
(Leonard:)I swear to God, I'm smart.
(Sheldon:)Get it together, man.
(Sheldon:)All right, let me show you
some of the features of the room.
(Sheldon:)First, windows. Conventional.
(Sheldon:)Open, closed. Open, closed.
(Sheldon:)Halfway open, or halfway closed...
(Sheldon:)...depending on
your philosophical bent.
Over here is my comic-book collection.
Feel free to browse.
(Sheldon:)There's a box of disposable
reading gloves on the nightstand.
(Elizabeth:)Good to know.
In here,
you'll find emergency provisions.